Guide to the Physics Department records, 1930-2005 RG0077
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Physics Department records
1930-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Dept. of Physics
RG0077
41.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes office files, memos, correspondence, course materials, staff papers, administration materials, conferences/workshops, and course syllabi.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, 4, and 5 are closed for 75 years from date of record creation. Series 8 contains confidential employee and faculty informaiton and must be reviewed by an archivist prior to use by researchers.
Series 3 is closed for 100 years from date of record creation. Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Physics Department. A small addition was added in February 2018 (Accession 2018.007).
Historical or Biographical Note
The Physics Department is a part of the Columbian College of Arts and Sciences. Physics, although not always called physics, was taught at Columbian College during the 1820s.
During the freshman and sophomore years, studies included English, Latin, and Greek; geography; arithmetic and algebra; history and antiquities; exercises in reading, speaking and composition; elements of chronology; rhetoric and logic; logarithms, geometry, trigonometry and mensuration; surveying, navigation, conic sections and Euclid's Elements. In his junior and senior years, the student took natural philosophy, astronomy, chemistry, fluxions, natural history, history of civil society, natural religion, Revelation, natural and political law, metaphysics, moral philosophy and analogy of religion to nature.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include office files, memos, curriculum lists, staff files, recommendations, correspondence, course materials, budget summaries, staff papers, university committee on research, student/faculty files, progress reports, contracts, administration materials, graduate applicants, speaker invitation letters, conferences/workshops, summaries of fiscal year, course syllabi. The collection covers the years 1930 to 2005. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
This collection is organized into nine series. Seven are office/departmental files differentiated only by their date of transfer to the archives; one is a series of facilities plan; one is a series of faculty records.
Washington (D.C.); Budget; Committees; Faculty; Students; Contracts; Conferences; Theoretical physics; George Washington University
- Office records, 1962-1989; Series 1; 10.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes office files, memos, curriculum lists, staff files, recommendations, etc. from 1962-89.
  - C. Werntz, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Physics: GW Research, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Search, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Leo Piilonen, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas E. Chapuran, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jefferey O. Kephart, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C. Jeff Martoff, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Graduate Program In Math and Sciences, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Dean's Council, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University Committee On Research, 07/1983-01/1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Geology Department Graduate Program Review, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Departmental Planning Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Academic Research Plan, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chairman, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Physical Plant Department, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal Year, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Phys Fac Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Staff Meetings, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Shop, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lab Expenses, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gyorgy Wolf, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - D. Young, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Students, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Memos from Vice President of Academic Affairs Frence, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Memos from Provost Johnson, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Memos from the President, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Memos from the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Committee on Research, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General Memos for Columbian College of Arts and Sciences, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Memos from Dean Lovett, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Registrar, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - GW Students, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Col coll Students, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Apparatus-Equipment List, 1973-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Physics Curriculum, 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Curriculum, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Library, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Physics Memos, 1964-1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Middle States SubCommittee on Research, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Applied Math, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Program Evaluations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Physics Graduate Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Tony Fonseca visit to GW, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Department Search Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research Assistant Professor Search Committee, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Inquiries/ Job, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Omar Benhar, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Daniel Berdichevsky, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Boris Blankleider, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marek Bleszynski, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Richard Brandenburg, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Carol T. Christou, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Cohen, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Zheng M. Ding, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ali Eskandarian, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Quamrul Haider, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - W-Y Pauchy Hwang, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - M. Javed Iqbal, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Tomasz Jaroszewicz, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chueng-Ryong Ji, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mohammad W Katoot, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Yasuro Koike, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Victor Kriss, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Temba E. Molalose, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Vinod K. Mishra, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Quang Tuong Phan, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Gamal Elsayed Shohaiep, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - David A. Sparrow, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Gerard Van Der Steenhoven, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - M.H. Ahsan, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sun Chongde, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Ning Li, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ying Liu, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Kumari S. Murthy, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gerassimos G. Petratos, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Charles F. Wild, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Mafooz, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ali Khalil, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - P Aloupogiannis, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Zvi Rozenberg, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Prakhya R. Sasi, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Richard J. Vojtech, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Ricardo O. Alarcon, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Ricardo Alarcon, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Salahuddin Ahmad, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Abdollah Abtahi, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Antonio Ambrosio, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - David A. Broido, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Stephen SC Cheng, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Michael J. Devereux, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Carl Monroe Edwards, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Ali Fazely, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Hani Gaballa, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Kevin L. Giovanetti, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Keith Alan Griffioen, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Arthur Dayle Hancock, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Piotr Jaracz, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Andreas Leiberich, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - William R. Leo, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Mahmoud Moussavi Madani, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Yasar Onel, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Sotirios Papadopoulos, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Surender Saini, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Stanley H. Stern, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Fayez M. Swailem, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Henry B. Wald, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Charles Steven Witsnant, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Piilonen and Martoff, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Bruce S. Flanders, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - John E. Wise, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Ronald Gilman, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Karl Von Reden, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Wolfgang Wilke, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - M.R. Phelps, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Donald R. Benton, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - George Ciangaru, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Haydeh Dejbakhsh, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Shalev Gilad, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Kohei Itoh, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - James Langenbrunner, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Subrata Nath, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bruce A. Peterson, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Chandra Pillai, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Kamran Vaziri, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Michael L. Webb, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Jon S. Wesick, undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Dr. Natalia Meshkov, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dr. James E Payne, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Gordon A Thomas, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dr. CW Chu, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Francis M Gasparini, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Professor John C Love, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Egon Marx, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Bruce Pipes, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Robert W Schmieder, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Donald D Thornton, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Richard M Wheeler, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Stuart Wolf, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Promising but too late, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Application For Position: Promising, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Pavel Winternitz, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Richard Weiner, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Vacancy Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Maintenance, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Office Expense, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - General Supplies, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Laboratory Supplies, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Special Equipment, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Special Equipment, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Summer Accounts: Lab Supplies, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Summer Accounts: Office Expense, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Summer Accounts: Office Expense, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Research Grant: Dr. Eisenstein, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Postage Meter, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Publication Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Equipment: Eisenstein, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Grant Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Donald Lehman, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Scott Matthews, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Physical Plant Services, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Telephone Services, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Herbert Jehle: Honor Dinner, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Dr. AJ Zuchelli: Memos, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Private Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Current Environment Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - William Parke Recommendations, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Postdoctoral Letters, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Telephone Statement, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bookstore Forms, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Grade Changes, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - University Fellow Awards, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Grant Information: Faculty Alert Bulletin, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Library: Reserve Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Request for Print and Duplicating Service, 06/1977-02/1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Memoranda, 06/1977-07/1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Recommendations: Dr. Hobbs, 10/1976-04/1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Recommendations: Dr. Parke, 10/1976-06/1978 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Intra and Interdepartmental Memorandum, 12/1976-06/1978 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Work Requests, 10/1975-06/1978 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Maintenance, 05/1977-06/1978 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Charles Barber, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Craig Futterman, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Memoranda, 01/1977-05/07/1977 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Office Expense, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budget Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory Supplies, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Special Equipment, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Maintenance, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Equipment, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - General Supplies, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Telephone Bills, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Interdepartmental Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Memos: Faculty Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Departmental Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Job Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Office Expense, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - General Supplies: Xerox, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - General Supplies, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Laboratory Supplies, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Equipment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Special Equipment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Summer Accounts, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Check and Order lost by GSA, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Air Products and Chemicals, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Maintenance, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Research Corp Equipment, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General Supplies, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Equipment, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Special Equipment, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Laboratory Supplies, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Equipment, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Office Expense, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Maintenance, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hobbs: Letters of Recommendation, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Teaching Fellowships, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - General Supplies, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Laboratory Supplies, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Equipment, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Telephone and Postage, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Office Supplies, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Office Supplies, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Domestic Travel, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Special Activities, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Despina A. Kalenderidis, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Letters, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Jien-Ming Gui Kuei, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - GTA and UFs, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Louis Hargenrader, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Li Yang, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Susan M. Smola, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mokhtar Dahou, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - David Tomkinson, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Christopher Paquette, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Manideepa Dasgupta, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Registration Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mohammad Emadi-Babaki, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gottfried Kraft, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Li Yang, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Jianmin Gui Kuie, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Physics: Graduate Student Advising, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Council Gen Exam, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Joe Himes, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ray Shirver, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Council Fellowship Exam, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - E-Lam Dyu, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Dr. Hobbs, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - R Radin, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Hobbs [1/4], undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Hobbs [2/4], undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Hobbs [3/4], undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Don Loflang Physics Exam, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Hobbs, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Registration, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Hobbs, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - PhD Students Info, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Herb, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - m Fatemi, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Mohammad Fatemi, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Jerome J Harkins, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - J Harkins, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Harkins, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Mr Malone, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - M Fatemi, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Whipple Exam: Bergmann, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Hobbs, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - WL Malone [1/2], undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - WL Malone [2/2], undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Clyde Dease, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Jerry Alderman, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Alderman, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Dease, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Himes, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Ray Shirven, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hobbs, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Dr. Hobbs [4/4], undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Dr. Habin, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Abigail Salyers, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Jerry Alderman, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Joe Himes, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Abagail Salyers, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Abigail Salyers, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Ray Shirven, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Clyde Dease, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Prof Prats, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Wendell Nix, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Pratip N. Raychowdhury, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Otto Bergmann, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Barry Berman, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dr. William Briscoe, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Eamon Harper, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Herman Hobbs, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dr. N Khatcheressian, 1986-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Yasuro Koike, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Donald Lehman, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Alireza Mokhtari, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dr. William Parke, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dr. J Peverly, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Morton Taragin, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dr. A Auchelli, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Office Papers, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Telecommunication Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Regret Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Inquiries: General, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Employment Application, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Curriculum Vitae: Applicants, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Office Expenses, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    General note
    52711
  - Office Supplies, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    54111
  - Ihab Joudeh, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Thomas Carter, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Li Yang, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Colin Seftor, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Furniture, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - PPD Maintenence and Repair, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    59115
  - Budget Summary, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Part-time Faculty, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Personnel Actions Forms, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Department Check Pick-up sign Sheets, 07/1984-06/1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lab Equipment, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    58532
  - Lab Supplies, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    54121
  - Lab Supplies, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lab Equipment, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - PPD Maint and Repair, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Information, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Minutes of Departmental Meetings, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Physical Plant Department, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Textbook Orders, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Telephone, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Arlington Electronic, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Francisco Prats, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - NSF: Account #235, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Copies Instructions, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Postage Meter Reading, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Newark Electronics, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Candy Hardware, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Radio Shack, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Equipment, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lab Supplies, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Office Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - General supplies, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Thompson and Cook, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Radio Wholesalers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Central Scientific, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Edmund Scientific Company, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Interdepartmental Procurements, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Fisher Scientific, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - JB Kendall and Company, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Pasco Scientific, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Delivery Invoices, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Mailing Info, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Federal Express, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Office Equipment, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Printing and Duplicating, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Office Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Office Supplies, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Facilities plan, 1989; Series 2; 1 Linear feet
  This series includes physics department machine shop plans from Jan. 1989.
- Office records, 1977-1990; Series 3; 7.5 Linear feet
  This series includes university committee on research, student/faculty files, correspondence, progress reports, contracts, and administration materials. They range in date from 1977-90.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
  - CEBAF, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CEBAF, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Honors Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University Committee on Research, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University Committee on Research, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Department of Energy Contract Materials, 1983-02/1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Progress Report Proposal: Original, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Progress Report Proposal: Original, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Department of Energy Contract/ Harper-Lehman-Prats, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Progress Report, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Renewal Proposal, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Renewal Proposal: Harper-Lehman-Prats, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Department of Energy Review Package: Harper-Lehman-Prats, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Department of Energy Review Package: Original, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Progress Report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Department of Energy Renewal Proposal: Harper-Lehman-Prats, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Proposal: Harper-Lehman-Prats, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Year 7, 02/1985-01/1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Year 6, 02/1984-01/1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Davis, Fred A., 12/1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Zubanov, Doug, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Coyne, John Joseph (Vita), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Araki, Minoru, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Info on Corcoran Hall Construction, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tocatlian, Marlaine, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Adhikari, Sadhan, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bakker, B. Lewis Gerrit, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Berthold, Gunther H., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Blankleider, Boris, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Blunden, Peter G., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Brandensburg, Richard, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bulgac, Aurel, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Carlson, Joseph A., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)